I just never thought
that being weak and powerless
could be so frustrating.
[Killua] Gon…
for the 30 days that you can't use Nen,
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
ONE WISH X AND X TWO PROMISES
to ask the Hunters for a favor.
His desperate wish
was that they save the dying queen.
[Netero] It's me. I want you to send over
the Chimera Ant research team immediately.
Contact Dr. Lee
of the Fanlin Medical College.
Have her assemble a team
of the best surgeons
and artificial organ engineering
specialists she can find.
-Hmm.
-[line disconnects]
Be ready to leave here in four hours.
[Morel and Knov] Yes, sir.
[both gasp]
[Netero] We will do
absolutely everything in our power.
And, Colt…
We're going to need your help
to accomplish this.
[grunts]
It is. His "heart" T-shirt.
[breathing deeply]
[Knov] I thought it was just a rumor.
your opinion on this matter
would be rather helpful,
It feels like little needles
stabbing all over my body.
I doubt…
that you'll be able
to lay a finger on him.
-[Morel] Huh?
-[Knov] Hmm?
[Colt] You'll be killed
by one of his Royal Guards
before you can even get close.
Now, Morel,
the pupils will be decided today, correct?
[Morel] Right.
Go with Colt and gather the victors
and research team together.
Then quickly get everyone
over to the nest.
And you, sir?
You can't pursue the King alone.
Don't forget my million, okay?
Oh, you'll get your money.
[Bihorn] Everyone else has already left.
[Panda Ant] Sure looks that way.
Most of our soldiers went off
and joined one of the other squads,
except for a handful
of oddballs that defected.
They all decided to stay here.
[instruments clattering]
Update me.
Were you the one who stopped the bleeding?
For the moment, we'll attach
as many artificial organs as we can.
Can you use my organs?
You can have all of my blood as well.
Chimera Ants from different generations
are completely different organisms.
Just look around you.
You'll see how much the Chimera Ants
in your own generation vary.
[grunts]
[Dr. Lee] Thank you nonetheless.
We promise to do our best.
[Queen] Is anyone there?
[Colt] Yes! I'm right by your side.
Is there anything you need?
[Morel] What is it?
-[Dr. Lee] A signal?
-[Octopus Ant] Correct.
The Queen is not capable of speech
like the rest of us are.
Can you interpret for me?
She may give us a hint
as to how to save her life.
[Queen] Tell me…
My son, how is he?
Is he all right?
"Anything at all?"
[Colt groans]
[Colt] Don't worry.
He is perfectly healthy, and right now…
Right now he's taken the Royal Guard
to look for herbs,
The truth is that after he killed
and ate some of the squad leaders,
he left to find a new territory.
[Knuckle] Huh?
[Queen] Then he's safe?
The King is safe?
[Colt] Yes.
[Queen sighs]
However, it appears that
I have finally fulfilled my destiny.
That's enough for me.
[Colt] What are you saying?
[Queen] I know my body
better than anyone else,
Even so, I have no regrets, not one.
[Colt] Please stop.
My queen, you have to live!
Use my body. It's the only way.
Come on! You have to try, at least.
Listen to her.
Respect her wishes. They may be her last.
[gasps]
[Queen] I have one final request.
A name?
Meruem.
him know.
[gasping]
[flatline tone ringing]
I failed to protect her again.
I'm useless.
I can't protect anyone.
[Panda Ant] No, he's probably referring
to a memory from when he was human.
If you've ever wondered
how we learned to talk so fast,
that's how.
[Morel sighs]
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
[Octopus Ant] Look!
There's something moving!
[Colt] Don't.
Stand back. I'll get it myself.
[gasps]
[crying]
this baby.
I swear it.
[Knov] Morel?
Colt, can you promise me
that neither of you will ever eat a human?
But if you're willing
to give me your word…
I won't let anyone harm you two,
not as long as I'm around anyway.
[chuckles]
There's no doubt about it.
[screaming]
Right. I'm over it now.
Knuckle and the other Hunters
are gonna save Kite, I'm sure of it.
So I have to get a whole lot stronger,
but the fact remains that we've spent
much more time with him than you have.
[gasps]
Then I'd tell you Kite wouldn't want
to see you two like this.
I'm positive that he's still alive,
and I'm absolutely certain he wouldn't
want the two of you to have any regrets.
The question is what to do now.
You should choose wisely
and find the will to follow through.
Yeah. You're right.
It's a species of bird
that only live around a certain mine.
No one's been able to figure out
exactly why that is yet.
The food, the water, the weather,
nothing really explains it.
So we bought the entire area
where the mine is located.
Or rather, where what's left of it is.
Kite financed it for us.
We were just kids
who had nothing to offer in return,
taking flight
with the light of dawn at their backs.
It's the most vivid and lasting memory
Stick and I have.
When we found out the area was
slated to become an industrial waste site,
we finally realized
how important all of it was to us.
To my treasure.
[footsteps approaching]
[both grunt]
[scraping, fluttering echoing]
[scraping, fluttering]
[gasps]
[groans]
I truly am the king of speed.
Given Cheetu's speed, it's a good bet
that he's already crossed the border.
Cows, pigs, humans, boars, bears.
I don't even care,
as long as they're plentiful.
Because I'm the king, the king of eaters.
in order to become kings themselves.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Date with Palm."
[singer singing in Japanese]